Back then,
we were just a ragtag gang following the Dragon-Seeking Clan.
Seeing the ground covered in gold and silver treasures,
thinking we'd make it big someday...
Tell me,
who wouldn't succumb to greed?
What happened next?
Then...
Zhang Tianyou.
You say the Evil Entity I saw doesn't exist.
Then what is the root cause of the tragic deaths of The Four Great Families?
It's all mine!
The root cause of all this...
is actually
the mysterious illness you contracted in this tomb back then.
No.
No, no, no!
The sins you committed here,
your greed,
your fear and selfishness...
That's the fate that led to all this.
What's more terrifying is
that you even passed this mysterious illness to your descendants.
Impossible.
You're still lying to me even now.
Patriarch Mei.
Look for yourself.
Even at a time like this,
you still don't believe it?
Gold with legs!
Come.
Fenglin!
Dad!
Come!
The king's throne is mine!
Fenglin!
Brother!
Chun'er!
I am Destined by Fate!
Destined my foot!
Chun'er!
Brother!
Brother, wake up!
Tell us now!
Miss Mei.
Fine.
Since you've always believed in the Evil Entity,
isn't the Evil Entity right here now?
No...
Then...
Dad!
Then,
we went into a killing frenzy.
We ignored the Zhang family's warnings,
and the Zhangs were forced into the fray as well.
In the end, only a few of us and Patriarch Zhang survived.
It was Patriarch Zhang, heavily injured,
who dragged us out of here, one by one.
When we woke up in the woods,
Patriarch Zhang
was already lying on the ground, covered in blood.
At the time, we saw the Book of Talismans and Incantations on him,
and the Celestial Seal.
Those are the greatest treasures in the world!
So we abandoned your father
and divided the treasures among ourselves.
He saved you,
yet you treated him like this.
Tianyou...
Later,
I turned back halfway on my own without telling them.
But your father's body was gone.
I searched and searched,
but I couldn't find him in the end.
It seemed he was dragged away by wild beasts.
A momentary lapse in judgment...
Can't blame me.
Can't blame me!
I'm begging you.
Zhang Tianyou.
Dad!
I'm begging you.
We elders committed these sins.
Please don't punish the next generation.
All I want is the whole truth.
Zhang Tianyou, I'm begging you.
Hurry and destroy this place!
Destroy it! I'm begging you!
Dad!
Nobody move!
The Evil God has already promised me.
He will grant me infinite power and authority.
The Dragon Scale Armor is on her now.
Let's see how you block my bullets!
Cheng Xiao.
Are you still unrepentant?
All of this is just your greed.
There is no Evil God at all.
Bullshit!
I won't be played by you again.
The Evil God has made a pact with me.
Soon, the whole world will be mine.
Go to hell!
Wait!
Li Xiao.
Do you really think the mysterious illness only infects The Four Great Families?
Did you forget?
Your father, Marshal Li, also went into the tomb back then.
You...
What do you mean?
Think about it carefully.
Who killed your father in the woods just now?
Son...
I... I'm your father.
Impossible.
I couldn't have killed my father!
Absolutely impossible!
Stop talking nonsense!
Ling Yu!
Zhang Tianyou...
I...
What the Sheng family and I owe you...
have paid in full.
Ling Yu
Tianyou, I'm the only one left in the Sheng family.
You'll protect me,
won't you?
The Qi and Sheng families have redrawn their territories.
What belongs to the Sheng family now is right here.
In the past, the Sheng family and I wronged you in many ways,
and hurt your pride.
This is a letter of divorce.
From now on, we have nothing to do with each other.